convert.com 2017-06-02

# Privacy Policy - A/B Testing Software

**EFFECTIVE DATE: March 23, 2016** (Old Privacy Policy)

Convert Insights, Inc. provides online website optimization services to our customers (the "Services") to improve the performance of their online business and marketing activities. We collect certain personally identifying information from our customers and their websites in the course of performing the Services. We respect the privacy of our customers and their customers. This privacy policy describes the measures taken by us to protect that privacy.

### WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT, AND WHEN DO WE COLLECT IT?

 **Information We Collect When You Register and Create An Account.** Visitors to our website ([www.convert.com](https://www.convert.com/)) (the "Site") may read information about us and our products and services without revealing any personally identifiable information. However, in order to become a customer, you must create an account and set up a profile. When you to this, we ask for your name, your organization's name, its street address and your e-mail address. We also require you to select a password. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and you may elect to provide additional information (e.g. a nickname and certain user preferences).

**Information We Collect From Your Websites.** The Services we provide consists of tracking visits to your website and collecting information about the behavior of those visitors. The data we collect helps you optimize your website and to use it strategically. This data may include the web addresses (URLs) of pages visited, the URLs of web pages that referred your visitors to your website, details about the web browsers that visitors to your website use to browse your website, the operating systems used by those visitors, the number of screen colors and the screen resolution used by the visitors to view your websites, and external geodata elements connected to your visitors' ip address, including country, city, region, etc. Our Service is organized so that our customers can specify the categories of data they wish to receive. The foregoing categories of information do not necessarily enable us or others to identify you or the visitors to your website. However, if the URLs we collect contain information that in themselves identify personally identifiable information, such as a name or phone number, or if they link to pages that contain personally identifiable information, then we may collect that information as well. 

**Other Information We Collect.** Our Service allows our customers to transmit and store additional information on our servers. This additional information can be anything, including personally identifiable information, except that we don't permit URLs or internet addresses to be stored. We have no control over what information is transmitted by our customers to our servers. Our customers may also request that we receive personally identifiable information that has been rightfully obtained by those customers, such as the email addresses of those who visit their websites and the information that visitors to their websites choose to post.

**Cookies.** A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. We use cookies to identify our customers, offering them access to their personalized accounts for our Services. We also use cookies to identify visitors who browse our customers' websites. These cookies contain an identifier that identifies each such visitor anonymously in order to be able to analyze his or her past behavior in relation to your website. None of our cookies contain or collect personally identifiable information.

### Basically

We track users for our test and targeting software but do not store IP addresses to figure out your identity.

### WHO OWNS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

All of the information that we collect, retain and store from our customers that identify them and the visitors to their websites belong to our customers. We treat that information as proprietary, confidential customer property. Convert Insights is merely a limited agent that possesses and uses the information only for purposes of performing the Services requested by our customers. We recommend that our customers include information in their own privacy policies that describes their use of hosted optimization services such as those we provide. We also recommend that each of our customers provides its visitors with information regarding their ability to opt-out of permitting disclosure of their personally identifiable information to providers such as Convert Insights. We urge visitors to our customers' websites to review the privacy policies of those websites. Those privacy policies govern the use of visitors' personally identifiable information by our customers and also by us.

### Basically

The data we collect is owned by our customers.

### Payment Services

To use the Services, you are required to pay the fees described on the Website by giving your credit card information and agreeing that Convert Insights may charge that credit card a monthly fee until you close your account. The monthly fee is set forth [www.convert.com/pricing/](https://www.convert.com/pricing/). Convert Insights may terminate your account or suspend provision of the Services in the event that a monthly charge is rejected by the credit card company. Convert Insights reserves the right to modify its billing terms, including payment and deposit requirements, at any time, and such modified billing terms will be reflected in an updated version of such terms posted on or linked from the Convert Insights Website or by e-mail notification to you. If you do not consent to such modified terms, you may renegotiate or terminate the program and the associated program terms at any time by providing written notice to Convert Insights within thirty (30) days of such notice; or you may direct Convert Insights to stop charging your credit card and to close your account. No refunds under any circumstances. All credit card details will be handled securely to ensure confidentiality and SSL encryption is employed to ensure sensitive data is protected. Convert Insights has a responds time for customer queries via email or telephone and we will respond within 48 hours.

### Basically

You pay and you credit card is secure, you get access. You stop paying we close your account.

### HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WE RECEIVE OR COLLECT?

We use the data we collect only for the purpose of performing the Services.

### Basically

We do not shop around with your name or data.

### WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

Other than as explicitly described in this privacy policy, we will not share the personally identifiable information we collect with any third party without the express written permission of our customers. Since the data belongs to our customers, we take our direction from them. However, we reserve the right to share the information that we collect with third parties in aggregated and/or anonymous form, and we will not necessarily ask for your permission or even inform you that we are doing so. We may also disclose information that we collect if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets, and, depending upon the transaction, the personally identifiable information of our customers or the visitors to our customers' websites may be among the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, the personal information we have collected may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

### Basically

We do not share data, unless we are forced to.

### HOW LONG DO WE RETAIN THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

We plan to retain the information that our customers store on our servers for three years. However, we will purge the information relevant to a particular customer or visitor to our customers' websites when we receive a request to do so. Our cookies retain active for one year.

### Basically

We store data three years and cookies stay active for one year.

### SAFE HARBOR DATA PRIVACY NOTICE

We comply with the US, EU, and US Swiss Safe Harbor and EU-US Privacy Shield Frameworks for protecting the privacy of data flowing from the EU and Switzerland to the United States, as set forth by the US Department of Commerce. 

We frequently enter agreements with our EU customers to provide them access to our Service, which includes the processing of information relating their customers. In providing our Service, we do not own, control or direct the use of the information stored or processed on our platform at the direction of our customers, our customer’s website visitor data is stored in Frankfurt Germany, our customer data (logins, marketing and email data as well as our CRM are stored in the US. We are largely unaware of what information is being stored on our platform and only access such information as reasonably necessary to provide the Service (including to respond to support requests), as otherwise authorized by our customers or as required by law. We are the data processors and not the data controllers of the information on our platform for purposes of the EU Directive on Data Protection (Directive 95/46/EC) and the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection. Our EU or Swiss based customers, who control their customer data and send it to Convert Insights Inc. products for processing, are the controllers of that data and are responsible for compliance with the Directive. In particular, our customers are responsible for complying with the Directive and relevant data protection legislation in the relevant EU member state before sending personal information to Convert Insights Inc. for processing. We work with our customers to help them provide notice to their customers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected. 

As the processors of personal information on behalf of our customers, we follow their instructions with respect to the information they control to the extent consistent with the functionality of our Service. In doing so, we implement technical, physical and administrative measures against unauthorized processing of such information and against loss, destruction of, or damage to, personal information as more fully described above under Protection of Information. 

To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Convert Insight’s certification, please visit [Export.gov](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/ "Safe Harbor Certification")

While the validity of the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework has been recently rejected by the EU Court of Justice and EU-US Privacy Shield yet to be implemented and tested, Convert Insights continues to adhere to its core principles, solely as a supplementary measure for further protecting and enhancing our Visitors’ and Users’ privacy (and without derogating from our commitment to follow all applicable legal requirements). If you have any questions about our Safe Harbor participation, please contact us using the information below.

### Basically

We do keep on the good side of every law in EU and US. We are Safe Harbor Certified.

### WHAT ARE THE OPTIONS TO CONTROL THE USE OF THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT IS SUBMITTED TO US?

Each of our customers is invited to place an opt-out link on their website that may be used by visitors to their websites who do not want their information given to Convert Insights. By clicking on the link, those visitors may activate our opt-out process. We will implement each opt-out election within five minutes of the time we receive it. We have placed a general opt-out on the home page of our Site. By using the general opt-out, our customers may direct us to purge all or a portion of the data that we have received or collected in the course of performing the Services. You may opt-out of our Services for each individual customer website and for all of our Services for all customer sites. We provide the opt-out functionality at: [www.convert.com/opt-out/](https://www.convert.com/opt-out/) Upon receiving your opt-out request, we will purge the information submitted to us pertaining to that request.

### Basically

We allow opt-out per customer or for all our services.

### HOW CAN OUR CUSTOMERS UPDATE THEIR PROFILES?

Our customers can help us maintain the accuracy of their profiles by notifying us when they change any of the contact information they submitted originally when they opened their accounts. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from us, you may visit [www.convert.com](https://www.convert.com/) contact and update your profile. Please include your current contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections.

### Basically

Keep your customer profile up to date.

### WHAT ELSE SHOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES?

 **Security.** The data we collect from our customers and their websites in the course of providing the Services is stored on servers operated by third parties under contract with us. The user names and passwords our customers use to access their accounts and the Services are stored on servers operated by different third parties, also under contract with us. No electronic information is ever absolutely secure. However, the third parties we use have instituted reasonable commercial measures to ensure the security of our customers' information, and we rely on the effectiveness of those measures to keep our customers' information secure. These security measures include physical security of the facilities where the servers are located; redundant storage of data in multiple physical locations; access to data based on established privilege levels; firewalls to prevent unauthorized access; and SSL-encrypted API calls. We do not collect, store or transmit any credit card or banking account data from sites installing our code. Data that our customers submit to us regarding visitors to their websites do not contain any personally identifiable information unless the visitors themselves have included such personally identifiable information in their submissions to our customers' websites. We have no control over this, and we disclaim any responsibility for the unauthorized use or disclosure of such information. However, such data is retained in the servers in anonymous form, ip address are not stored.

Links to Other Sites. Our Site contains hyperlinks and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. These links are provided for your reference only. We do not control, operate or endorse in any respect information, products or services on such third-party sites and are not responsible for their content. Many third-party sites have their own privacy policies that differ from ours. This privacy policy only covers our Site and does not cover any other site. While we make every effort to keep your information secure, we do not control the policies of other sites.

### Basically

We work hard to keep you and your clients anonymous.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may make changes in our privacy policy from time to time. When we do so, we will post the revised privacy policy on our Site with a link at the bottom of our home page. Our home page will also contain a statement notifying readers that the policy has changed and the effective date of that change.

### Basically

We update this privacy policy monitor it well.

### CONTACTING CONVERT INSIGHTS

You may contact us with any comments or questions about our privacy policy and practices using the following contact information: By email: [info@convert.com](mailto:info@convert.com)

### Basically

Need to contact us email to [info@convert.com](mailto:info@convert.com)

### ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

Your use of our Site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. **BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE.** We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

### Basically

By using the site you agree to this privacy policy.

### EFFECTIVE DATE

The effective date of this version of the privacy policy is November 20, 2009. This privacy policy was last revised on December 9, 2015.

### Basically

We are around since 2009 so is this privacy policy.

Scroll
